https://www.daf.qld.gov.au/site-information/privacy

Integrity framework
Economic recovery—support for Queensland producers announced
Agriculture
Topics: Drought and disaster recoveryAnimalsPlantsQueensland's primary industries trendsAgriculture research, development and extension (RD&E)...
Biosecurity
Topics: Animal biosecurity and welfarePlant biosecurityInvasive plants and animalsEnhancing biosecurity capability and capacity in QueenslandBiosecurity policy, legislation and regulation...
Fisheries
Topics: Aquaculture Fisheries habitatsRecreational fishingCommercial fishingCharter fishing...
Forestry
Topics: State native forestry businessState-owned quarry materialResponsibilities of governmentForest and timber industry profilePrivate native forestry...
Contact us
Customer service centre
Compliments and complaints
Topics: Public interest disclosures
Enquiries
Office operating hours
Topics: Research stations and facilities
Staff messages
News and media
Media centre
Topics: Ministerial statementsDepartmental media releases
Newsletters
Topics: Agriculture newsAquaculture updateBiosecurity newsCultivateCatch news...
Alerts
Topics: Agriculture alertsBiosecurity alerts
Social media
Podcasts
Topics: Eradicating varroa mites – the sweetest successSIPS: A licence to fishWorkplace health management plans: COVID-safe farmsAgTech: Where agriculture meets technologyFood pilot plant: Making food dreams come true...
Campaigns
Topics: AgTechCheck your baitSharkSmartSustainable beef#eatqld
Website information
Help
Copyright
Disclaimer
Privacy
Accessibility
HomeWebsite informationPrivacy
Privacy
Your privacyThe Department of Agriculture and Fisheries is committed to protecting user privacy. We understand and appreciate that visitors to, and users of, this website are concerned about their privacy and the confidentiality and security of information they provide to us. As part of the Queensland Government, this department has responsibilities under the Information Privacy Act 2009 regarding the collection, use, storage and disclosure of personal information. The Act also provides access and amendment rights for personal information held by the department.Information about the types of personal information the department holds is contained in our Privacy guide
(PDF, 157.1KB) publication. This guide also provides information on how to obtain access to a document containing personal information and the process for lodging a privacy complaint.Management logsWhen you visit this website, our server makes a record of your visit and logs information for statistical purposes only. This information includes, the user's server address, the user's top level domain name (for example .com, .gov, .au, etc), the date and time you visited the site, the pages accessed and documents downloaded, the previous site visited, and the type of browser you use.No attempt will be made to identify users, or their browsing activities, unless we are lawfully required to do so for investigation or law enforcement purposes.Links to other sitesThis website contains links to other websites. The Department is not responsible for the content, security and privacy practices of these websites.CookiesA cookie is a message given to a web browser by a web server. The browser stores the message in a text file called cookie.txt. The message is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server.The main purpose of cookies is to identify users and possibly prepare customised web pages for them. When you enter a website which is using cookies, you may be asked to fill out a form providing such information as your name and interests. This information is packaged into a cookie and sent to your web browser which stores it for later use. The next time you go to the same website, your browser will send the cookie to the web server. The server can use this information to present you with custom web pages. This website uses cookies to store information only. If you have configured your browser to reject all cookies you will still be able to generally browse through the site.How the site handles email correspondence and feedback informationThis is a Queensland Government website. Email correspondence sent to email addresses on this site, or information submitted via web forms on this site, will be treated as a public record and will be retained as required by the Public Records Act 2002 and other relevant legislation. It will also be subject to the provisions of the Right to Information Act 2009 and the Information Privacy Act 2009.Your name and address details will not be added to a mailing list nor will we disclose these details to third parties without your consent (except for correspondence to public email lists) unless required by law. Email messages may be monitored by our information technology staff for system trouble-shooting and maintenance purposes.Obtaining access to your personal informationIf you want to access your personal information that is in the custody and control of the department, please email Right to information Services: rtiservices@daf.qld.gov.au.Making a privacy complaintIndividuals who are concerned that their privacy has not been dealt with in accordance with the Information Privacy Act 2009 can submit a complaint in writing to the department. The complaint should outline the basis for the complaint in as much detail as possible and include an address to which notices and correspondence may be sent during the complaint process. Privacy complaints should be sent to:Privacy Contact OfficerDepartment of Agriculture and Fisheries Level 31, 400 George Street, Brisbane GPO Box 2454 Brisbane QLD 4001privacy@daf.qld.gov.auIf the complaint has not been dealt with satisfactorily, or the department has not responded, you may then make a privacy complaint to the Office of the Information Commissioner. The privacy complaint will then be mediated if deemed appropriate, or may be referred to the Queensland Civil and Administrative Tribunal. A privacy complaint may not be made to the Information Commissioner until at least 45 days after the complaint has been made to the department. The postal address of the Information Commissioner is:Office of the Information CommissionerPO Box 10143Adelaide StreetBrisbane QLD 4001Please email our Privacy team for more information on privacy@daf.qld.gov.au.
Last updated:
09 Dec 2018
Feedback
Contact us 13 25 23
Follow us:
Is your feedback:
This page was:
useful not useful
Your feedback about this page
Your contact details (email or phone)
I'm looking for...
RBE (Registerable Biosecurity Entity)
